cheltenham-festival.co.uk 2014-12-14

# Cheltenham Festival About Us | Advertising | Privacy Policy

Our Platform, [Cheltenham Festival](http://www.cheltenham-festival.co.uk/) is one of the platforms owned by us and our company name is Moneta Communications Limited. All our sites offer information on many sporting events primarily in the UK. We provide our readers with free sports betting news, odds, tips and free bets with our gaming partners in the online gaming sector.

## Privacy Policy

We would like to advise all our customers that your privacy is our top priority. We run promotions occasionally and it is important that you are aware of the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. Please find below our privacy policy. We are [Moneta Communications Limited](http://www.moneta-communications.com/) and we own and operate this website (www. cheltenham-festival.co.uk), our registered address is Tower House, Parkstone Road, Poole, Dorset, BH15 2JH. Please read the following policy to understand how we will deal with your personal data after it has been collected by us through your use of one of our platforms. Those platforms include our website, and any other channels as they evolve.

The operator of this website, Moneta Communications Limited, is committed to protecting your privacy. References to "we", "us" and "our" in this Policy are references to this site [www.cheltenham-festival.co.uk](http://www.cheltenham-festival.co.uk/). This Policy describes what happens to the information which you supply to us, where that information identifies you individually :- e.g. your name and address details.

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time.

Website Administration:  
Business Name : Moneta Communications Ltd  
Address : 31 Sleaford Close, Office One, Bury  
Post Code : BL8 1XF  
Country : England  
Website URL : http://www.cheltenham-festival.co.uk  
Website email : info@betting-directory.com  
Tel: 0161 797 1036

Compliance with legislation:

We operate and are registered in accordance with all applicable data protection legislation in England and Wales. Collection of data. We are mainly aiming this web site at the UK and EU market, but we cannot guarantee that it accords with local laws of any other countries (though we will try to make sure it does).

We may collect data about you, some of which could be personal, in a variety of ways, including:

  * when you register with the website;
  * when you enter competitions and/or complete surveys; and
  * through the use of certain data capturing devices (for example studying which pages you read the most through the use of cookies).
  * we have designed this web site so that users of all ages will be able to use the site. However, some content of this web site may be more appropriate for persons over 18 years of age. You agree that any use of this web site by persons under 18 years of age shall be done with constant supervision from a responsible adult such as a parent or guardian.

## Use of personal data

We may ask you to submit personal data to this web site (for example your name, address and contact details) to enable us to enter in our competitions or provide you with the services available through this web site. This information will be kept securely in accordance with our internal security policy and may be used, stored and processed to improve the operation, administration and development of the web site as well as for marketing, advertising and promotional purposes, but only in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

## Terms of Use

This website is protected by international Copyright. Copying, duplication or reproduction of content by any means whatsoever is strictly prohibited without the prior written permission of Moneta Communications Limited.

Commercial Exploitation: The information contained herein, including text, images and photographs, must not be copied, adapted, distributed or otherwise used for commercial gain. Any such action would establish liability for a civil action and may give rise to criminal proceedings.

Copyright © 2004 - 2008 Moneta Communications Ltd

If you are from outside of the European Union or if you do not agree with these Terms of Use, please do not access and use the rest of this web site.

This site in no way wishes to infringe on anyone's copyright. It is our policy to make every effort to respect the copyrights of outside parties. If you believe that your copyright has been misused, please email us and we will remove the picture(s) or acknowledge the source, as soon as we receive your email. In view of this, please do not submit any material to us that you do not hold copyright over or have permission to distribute freely.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Whenever you visit our website (unless you elect not to receive cookies), then your computer will store an identifying code in the cookie. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.

We use cookies to help us (i) estimate and report our total audience size and traffic (ii) conduct research to improve our content and services (iii) to make your user experience more simple in a variety of different ways, for example you do not need to type in your user name each time you return to the site.

Please note that we allow other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not our Privacy Policy.

## Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Website are delivered to you, on our behalf, by our web advertising partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads.

## Links/Third Parties

Please note that this privacy policy only addresses our activities from our servers. Other sites (including those our website links to and third party sites or services) may have their own privacy policies and practices, which we do not control.

While we strive to protect your personal information, our network of sites contain links to partners, advertisers and third party Internet sites and services who may collect data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, e-commerce, etc. They each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of our policy and therefore we have no control over these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for their privacy practices or the content of such websites.

## Consent

By disclosing your personal information to us using this website, you consent to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by us in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

## Opt-Out Policy

Registered users of the website who have elected to receive our newsletter always have the option to opt-out of receiving further information from us by clicking on the link at the end of each newsletter and via the website.

## Amendments to this Policy

We may amend this policy from time to time however we assure you that we only use your data and for our legitimate business reasons and in order to give you a better user experience. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our homepage.

## Testimonials

Some information and e-mails sent to us may be used as testimonials but no e-mail address or contact details will be displayed.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the information we hold about you, please feel free to contact us.
